marutisuzukiastar.com 2011-05-16

# Privacy Policy :: Maruti Suzuki A-Star: Stop at nothing with KB series Engine

|  |   
---  
|   
---  
  
##  At Maruti Suzuki we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our terms and conditions. 

  * This covers Maruti Suzuki's treatment of personally identifiable information that Maruti Suzuki collects when you are on MarutiSuzuki site and when you use our services. This policy also covers Maruti Suzuki's treatment of any Personally identifiable information that Maruti Suzuki shares with you. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Maruti Suzuki does not own or control or Maruti Suzuki does not own or employ or manage. 

  * Maruti Suzuki collects personally identifiable information when you register for a Maruti Suzuki account. When you choose the services and promotions.   
Maruti Suzuki may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners. 
  * When you register with Maruti Suzuki, we ask for your name, e-mail address, birth date, gender, occupation, industry and personal interest. Once you register with Maruti Suzuki and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * Maruti Suzuki uses information for three general purpose: to fulfill your requests for certain products and services and to contact you about specials and new products. 

  * Maruti Suzuki will not sell or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to anyone. 
  * Maruti Suzuki will send Personally Identifiable Information about you when: 
  * We have consent to share the information 
  * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested 
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process. 
  * When we find your action on the web site violates the Maruti Suzuki terms and condition or any of your usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

  * Your Maruti Suzuki account information is password-protected for your privacy and security 
  * We have taken adequate measures to secure access to your personal data 

  * Maruti Suzuki may edit this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
